I've come out we're gonna do a segment
right now called agree or disagree I'm
gonna read you a statement about comedy
you tell me if you agree with it or
disagree with this okay
pretty simple agree or disagree don't
bring a drink onstage if you're only
going to do a short set oh I disagree I
don't think there's any rules about that
no I love having a drink no matter what
I'm just afraid I'm gonna get dry mouth
even though I never do yeah why don't
have that drink and play that's usually
booze
I want my booze at all times yeah and
you know I think there's nothing wrong
with that now I wish on late night sets
when I you know when you do those five
minutes I wish you could have water with
you because half of those people are
just five people fighting drive you can
used to be like it's part of my set okay
I guess he needs that and then you can
oh yeah great they'll do whatever you
want if you just press them yeah how
many late-night sets have you done like
those five minute spots on like
Letterman or Conan or whatever all
America I would I haven't done one in
years
all right like when I did my last when I
was like I'll never do this again this
was as good as it's gonna get yeah I'd
say maybe ten uh-huh overall yeah I
never have been good haven't been bad
what was the first one the first one I
did premium blend on Comedy Central
right really late night set but then I
didn't Kimmel and that went great within
like two weeks later because when you
get the money from premium blend that I
you're now in this guilt you're an Astra
or sag so you get all the money but next
time you do something we're gonna take
it off because you're hey so I got the
Kimmel checking it was for $5.00 and I
was like oh I'm screwed right I took it
thing on Carson Daly and I bombed so
badly that the band heckled me was not
the band that was gonna perform next but
the band Carson Daly the house band yeah
so what like like playing their
instruments in between jokes really what
will you like pissed at them I
was like I was just like do what you
gotta do right the best that we can yeah
my first one was live at Gotham which
was what premium blend became and then
Kim with lesser extent do a lot was it I
don't know I feel like we they really
pay more man's premium blend I don't
know premium blend premium blends better
than anything it's in the name
alright you know what some kids who call
itself premium it's feeling really
confident I still like to use it as my
main I mean Creta premium blend yeah and
then Kimmel and Kimmel was like okay I
got a good reaction but I was screaming
the entire time inside your head no I
was like very loud screaming into the
mic outside my head okay yeah I was very
nervous yeah it sounds like a disaster
no I got laughs it was okay but it's
like impossible for me to watch now cuz
I could see that I am a man or crisis
yeah I don't go back and watch those
yeah
agree or disagree don't worry about
being funny
just be you wow that's a tough one
because if you're doing stand-up comedy
what have you isn't funny
then yeah I disagree you shouldn't be a
comedian yeah I think you have to be
funny if you're doing comedy I would
never like if that guy was great he was
just him like yeah it wasn't funny but
you see how him II well yeah oh that was
he was that guy that is not funny
agree or disagree the more agents you
have in a crowd
the better the crowd Oh disagree
disagree my god agents Beck I'm coming
I'm like why don't go do not waste the
seat please do not come agree disagree
accents can be funny oh wow oh I agree
you agree yeah has anyone ever tried to
get you to like I mean you have a
natural act yes how often have like four
percentage of the time do auditions
where someone's like can you do it has
not happened in a long long long time
but it used to happen often enough that
I made a decision that I would not do
that has anyone ever asked you to lose
the accent like can you do like an
American accent no no this is it this is
it this is all I accept it
Australian actors you would never know
what their real act they're so you don't
think of yourself as a relaxed you're
like I'm Kumail I'm looking I can do
this yeah
gosh yeah I was it happened so much that
I decided I wouldn't do that
and once the cameras are done rolling
I'll tell you the last time that it did
happen to me and I said no
[Music]